<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DotsNLines</string>
    <string name="start_game">New game</string>
    <string name="board_size">Select a board size</string>
    <string name="instructions_label">HOW TO PLAY</string>
    <string name="board_size_prompt">Please select a board size</string>
    <string name="score_placeholder">0</string>
    <string name="points_label">\ point(s)</string>
    <string name="player_1_turn">Player 1\'s turn!</string>
    <string name="player_2_turn">Player 2\'s turn!</string>
    <string name="tie_game">It\'s a tie!</string>
    <string name="player_1_wins">Player 1 Won!</string>
    <string name="player_2_wins">Player 2 Won!</string>
    <string name="page_label_footer">/ 6</string>
    <string name="how_to_play_figure">how to play figure</string>

    <string name="instruction_1">Welcome to DotsNLines! The goal of the game is to score more
    points than your opponent by "closing" more squares.

    \n\nPlease swipe through the pages for more instructions on how to play!</string>

    <string name="instruction_2">To begin your move, tap any of the grey dots. It will then turn
        green to indicate the first "end-point" for your move. Then, select a grey dot directly
        adjacent to the green one (directly above, below, to the left or to the right).

        \n\nTap the green dot again to cancel that move.</string>

    <string name="instruction_3">To score a point, you must "close" a 1X1 square. A dot of your
        color will then appear to indicate that the square has been awarded to you as a point and the
        meter at the bottom of the board will update to reflect the score difference.

        \n\nPlease note that once a score is awarded, that 1X1 square can no longer be used to
        earn points.
    </string>

    <string name="instruction_4">Once you score a point, you earn an extra move and can continue
        making moves until you do not earn a point.

        \n\nPlease note that though you may be able find an opportunity to earn 2 points on one
        move (two adjacent 1X1 squares), this will still only earn you ONE extra move.
    </string>

    <string name="instruction_5">Plan ahead and play strategically! The larger the board, the more
        opportunities to score (or to help your opponent find a streak!)
    </string>

    <string name="instruction_6">The game ends when all possible moves have been exhausted.

        \n\nDepending on the size of the board, a tie may be possible, however in most cases, the
        game will end with one player having more points than the other. The player with the most
        points wins!

        \n\nAnd most importantly, ENJOY!
    </string>
    <string name="return_to_menu">return to menu</string>
</resources>
